Hey, luckiest kid in the
world who got to become my student.
Hello, my beloved master!
I won't hold back on you.
Are you ready?
Yes, please!
I welcome any difficult training!
If you hold back, I'll cry.
So, what do we start with?
A three-dimensional magic circle?
Or an oblique magic circle?
My request is the 50-section
compound spell!
INCREDIBLE TRAINING
AND INCREDIBLE RESULTS
What?
Man, thanks for the help.
I was looking for someone who can
make clean copies of my memos.
All of these?
And there'll be more.
Don't you love me anymore?
I never have.
So merciless and cool!
These here are state secrets.
You stay outside until he's done.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Please don't worry about me.
I'm rooting for you.
Thank you.
Hey, make me that thing.
Master sure loves this thing.
All right!
Shall I make you some tea?
I have a favor to ask of you.
Sword training?
Yes.
I've only just begun,
and I have much to improve.
I want to practice whenever
I have spare time.
Please do not tell Kunon about this!
Yes, Your Highness.
Pardon me!
I must become someone
suitable for Kunon.
A diagram?
Are you done yet?
About halfway.
You're slow.
Don't say that with such luminous skin.
I'm exhausted from trying
to decipher your scrawls.
My memos, you mean.
This letter looks just like an
earthworm writhing by the wayside
because it carelessly came out
of the comfort of damp ground.
Don't you compare my wisdom
with a hopeless situation.
May I send you an invoice for my work?
Stop complaining.
This is significant training, all right?
Information and knowledge are different.
What you can gain from
reading is just information.
What you analyze in your head
and write with your own hand,
your body remembers.
It becomes knowledge that's wildly
different from information.
And knowledge becomes power.
That's my master! I love you!
See ya. Make sure to finish
everything by next time.
Yes, sir.
Oh, there was a memo of a diagram.
Was it some sort of spell?
That one... It'll be quicker to show you.
Next time, you come to me.
What? Okay.
I'm happy that I get to see you often,
thanks to Master visiting me here!
Same here.
Don't confuse the means with the end.
Oh, Kunon.
Did you grow taller?
Yes, I'm ten years old now.
A growth spurt.
Your magical power has
become a bit stronger, too.
Is that true?
Wanna do another magic battle with me?
No way!
Kunon promised that he'd do a
flying magic experiment with me.
No, it's my turn.
You all get out of my way.
He's here to see me.
You're monopolizing him again?!
Not fair!
Follow me.
Yes, sir!
Is he taking Kunon to that room?!
You mustn't go!
That place is the world of demons!
Make that thing, now.
You know what magic tools are, right?
Yes. They're tools that work with
a sorcerer's magical power.
Right. For example, this lamp
is a magic tool of fire.
Magical engineers are sorcerers who
make their living by creating magic tools.
Magical engineers.
Wow! It's amazing!
Are all of these your scrawls, Master?
You mean memos.
This is a spell I've never tried out.
I wanted this grimoire so much
that I tried to rely on Father's
collusion with His Majesty!
Master, I want to live here!
You don't need to use
collusion or live here.
Eventually you can have it all.
Master! I love you!
This is the magic tool
I'm developing right now.
It's what was in the diagram.
Wow!
When it's completed, you can eat
a piping-hot meal in your own room
without going to the kitchen.
You can bake an apple pie in your room?
That's nice!
My earth magic is good
for modeling shapes,
but the fine details and
soft parts are not so easy.
Soft parts... Do you think
my water magic can make them?
You pick up quickly.
Eventually, you'll help with my work,
which will double as experiments.
That sounds fun!
Right?
Kunon Gurion!
Hello, Grand Master.
I've been waiting for you!
As promised, why don't we discuss
the essence of magic over lunch?
Make that thing.
My earth magic can take care of
reinforcing the outer frame, but...
Indeed. And water magic might be better
for the small internal mechanism.
My goodness, Kunon's
bed is nice, very nice.
Listen, Kunon.
If you want to change your teacher,
don't hesitate to speak up.
I'm being worked to the bone,
but he's a wonderful master.
And water and earth are quite compatible.
I couldn't have asked anyone better,
and I'm grateful to the Grand Master.
That's quite enough.
Are you embarrassed because your
beloved student admires you?
It's all right. Let us show
them how close we are!
Oh, really...?
For my personal safety, stop it.
What about Her Highness?
Since I'm here, I'd love
to have some tea with her.
Mirika is at the entrance ceremony
of the senior school for nobles today.
She was very disappointed
she couldn't see you.
Oh, her higher education has started.
And what do you plan to do?
If it's necessary,
I'll take the graduation exam.
I mean the magic school.
The magic school?
It's a school where bright sorcerers from
all over the world attend and learn.
All the Royal Sorcerers here
are graduates of that school.
You have to be twelve or older to enroll.
You still have time,
but give it some thought.
A school where sorcerers from
all over the world attend...
TWO YEARS LATER
A-ori.
Compound spell, 55 sections!
Good!
You did it.
Yes, sir!
It's right out of the oven and so tasty!
This magic tool is quite popular,
so I'm sure quite a bit of money
is going into Master's pocket.
Only Master's pocket.
May I get paid for my work after all?
I allowed you to do
experiments money can't buy.
I'll support your livelihood,
Master Kunon.
I know your talent better than anyone.
You sound like the lover of
a struggling stage actor.
Will you abandon me
when you're successful?
I will never do that.
I'm devoted to you.
Let's get married in the future.
Wow, so monotonous.
Sounds fake.
You've collaborated on seven
magic tools already, right?
Yes. And five papers on
new theories on magic.
We also made a manual
for magic experiments,
and we're currently working
on another magic tool.
I can do the rest by myself.
What?
But we're codeveloping the Chest
that Draws in a Bunch of Bugs.
"Bunch of" sounds unprofessional.
Call it the Insects Box.
How are we completing the
Bunch of Insects Box?
I said no "bunch of."
You're turning twelve this
spring, aren't you?
Huh? Yes.
I'm telling you to get ready
to go to the magic school.
The magic school?
I don't want to go.
What?
I don't need to go, because
I have you, Master.
I want to learn magic by your
side and get worked to the bone!
You've finished making the clean copies
of my memos and blueprints
of magic tools, right?
You're abandoning me because I'm done?
I'm not playing along.
I'm an earth sorcerer.
I can't teach water magic.
Still, I want you to...
What if there's an extraordinary
water sorcerer at the magic school?
The world is much bigger than Hughlia.
An extraordinary water sorcerer...
Right. Three-star, or if you're
lucky, maybe even four-star.
But... I...
Please go.
And become an amazing sorcerer.
I'll become a fine woman who is
worthy of you and wait for you.
Your Highness.
Very well.
I will go to the magic school.
Good.
Where is it?
What?! That far?! I change my mind!
Shut up! Go!
What exactly do I need to do to
prepare for the magic school?
Should I take a change of clothes
and the pillow I use every day?
You have something much more important.
I do! A gentleman's sense of humor!
You could have said my
lessons or something.
Your eyes.
Yes. That's right.
Master Kunon?
How did I forget?
My biggest ambition, my fervent wish...
The most important
purpose that I live for!
It's because I've learned to do
so many things without seeing.
Somewhere in my heart, I felt
I could just go on like this.
I'm such a fool!
I hate it! I can't do this!
You played it cool in
front of your boyfriend,
so stop crying already,
you pain in the— Ouch!
In the last two years, Kunon has
built his track record as a sorcerer.
If he gains sight through his magic,
he'll go down in history as the first person
to have achieved such a feat.
If he goes far away,
I might get left behind.
Sir Dario.
Yes?
Part of me can't help but wish that
Kunon's eyes will never see,
so that he'll stay by my side.
I am a despicable woman.
Yeah, you are—
Ow!
How many times do you have to do that?
You can voluntarily shut up,
or I can shut you up. It's your choice.
Your Highness, there's light
and darkness in our hearts.
But please don't get swallowed by
either and choose the right path.
Sir Dario.
It will be fine.
What you've been training for the
last two years isn't just your body.
Right.
Aren't you too lenient on your student?
You're too strict with your student.
You drive him into the ground
and then abandon him in the end?
The compound spell of 55 sections, the three-dimensional magic circle,
the anchored cylindrical magic
circle, imaginary codes,
rheologic sand patterns,
and magic tools. I taught him all of those!
Aren't I the best master there is?
If Master Kunon uses those,
will his eyes be complete?
No idea.
Don't tell me that you just
fed him a bunch of nonsense...
Watch it! Your darkness is showing!
Even I've never heard
of how to make eyeballs.
From here on, it's up to Kunon.
I've no doubt he'll do it.
After all, he's my beloved
student I'm proud of.
A-ori.
A mirror that reflects everything.
Master said that the eye of an insect is
a cluster of over ten thousand mirrors.
But even if they reflect a whole lot,
nothing transmits to me.
A-rubu.
This isn't it, either.
Hmm...
None of these is it.
What are you doing in
the middle of the night?
Come join me in the sauna.
Sure! Did you invite Father?
I'd hate to wake him up.
It's worse not to wake him up!
Father absolutely adores
the sauna you create.
Oh, is it sauna time?
Shh, you'll wake Mother.
No, it's worse not to wake her up.
A-ori.
Ah, that hits the spot!
Ale is the best!
What a good, manly drinker she is.
But I love you.
This is the best way to refresh.
It must be a real challenge
if you're stuck.
It's the biggest experiment
I've done so far.
Your eyeballs?
Yes. I'm nowhere near close.
If you need a breather
again, let me know anytime.
Know that I am at your disposal.
Thank you very much.
Everyone's so good to me.
I can't want to see their faces.
What do their faces look like?
I want to see what they see.
A-ori.
A-rubu.
The core is the water mirror.
I applied a rheologic sand
pattern on the surface
so that the pattern could read the
moving view and send it to my mind.
A-ori.
There's no complex configuration
or relaying mechanism.
All I had to do was to think simple,
without worrying about numbers and range.
I can see.
So this is the view.
This is vision.
I did it.
I can see. I can see. I did it.
I made eyeballs with magic!
Huh?
What?
NEXT EPISODE: KUNON THE SORCERER CAN SEE
Next episode: "Kunon
the Sorcerer Can See."